ICICI Lombard Q2 results: September quarter
profit declined by 2.2%
to ₹5773 crore ICICI Lombard has
announced a dividend for its shareholders The
company will pay an interim dividend of ₹1 per equity share The
private sector
insurance company's net premium income stood at ₹4306 crore as against ₹3836 crore
in the year-ago quarter
CII Lombard General Insurance has announced its second quarter results for the
financial year 2023-24 today on 18 October The
company's net profit in the July-September quarter was
₹57.3 crore,
down 2.2 per cent from ₹90.5 crore in the same period a year ago The company
released its quarterly results after market hours ICICI Lombard shares
fell 0.026 per cent to
close at ₹0 today on 18 October Dividend announced
ICICI Lombard has
announced a dividend for its shareholders The company will pay an interim dividend of
₹1 per equity share
Private sector insurance company to pay interim dividend Net
premium income stood at Rs 4,306 crore as against Rs 3,836 crore in the year-ago quarter
The stock has declined by over 1 per cent in the past month.
It has delivered a return of 26 per cent in the past six months The
company's shares have gained around 10 per cent so far this year,
while investors have
gained around 20 per cent in the past year
Changes in the company's SMP approved Based on the
recommendation of the Board Nomination and Remuneration Committee, the Board has approved
changes in the company's senior management personnel. As part of the
change in the organisational structure, Vice President Amit
Gupta is being designated as the SMT of the company. In
addition, existing
SMPs like Deepak Negi, Mukul Kamboj and
Hemant Singla will now report to Amit Gupta
and hence, they will no longer be SMPs of the company.